

# Lesya Stulkivska



# Junior FrontEnd Developer

## **Address**

Horishni Plavni, Poltava region, Ukraine

## **Phone**

+38097-994-77-86

### **Email**

jamma@i.ua



# **Skills**

## HTML5

CSS3/SASS

JAVASCRIPT/ES6

**REACT** 

**REDUX** 

**REST API** 

**WEBPACK** 

**GIT/GITHUB** 

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**FIGMA** 

# **Professional Summary**

Solution-driven, high-motivated Front End Developer ready to become a part of the team and work for a common result. Would like to grow up and pump professional skills on real projects. My goal is to become a Middle Front End Developer in two years.



# **Work History**

### 2013-07 -Manager

Sewing manufacture, Horishni Plavni, Poltava region

- Ensured new material shipments at different stages of manufacturing to align with procurement expectations.
- Managed production schedules and arranged timely delivery according to orders.
- Arranged for proper storage and inventory of products.
- Implemented stock inventory software.
- Developed an online store on Tilda.

## 2011-10 -2013-06

Current

# Typesetter

Newspaper "TE", Horoshni Plavni, Poltava region

- Prepared visual and textual materials for production.
- Utilized different technologies, including Adobe InDesign, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Photoshop, to ready artwork for offset printing purposes.
- Generated prepress proofs in digital or other formats to approximate appearance of final printed piece.
- Worked collectively with various partners such as designer, editor, journalist and management team to reach deadlines and meet customer expectations.



## Education

2006-09 -2011-06

Master of Science | **Computer Technologies of Publishing** Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics

2020-10 -Current

No Degree | Fullstack Development GolT Online



English - A2/B1

Language